JIMMY NILSSON, SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Driven and goal oriented software developer with +5 years of experience. Have co-founded and been the Lead Programmer at Tarhead Studio. Winner of multiple game awards and have released multiple games. I now feel like it is time to move on from the company I co-founded after our latest release I feel like it is time to try something new.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• C#, .NET, Unity3d, git, NUnit, Jenkins, SQL, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript.

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

Tarhead Studio AB, Lead Programmer

Aug 2013 - Present

- Managed planning and made sure the team could be as effective as possible, the programming team consisted of both remote and onsite members so a big part of the work was to make sure the communication was working between all team members.
- Implemented an automatic build system using jenkins, that increased number of builds per week from 2 per week to 10 per day. This helped us catch bugs faster and ship with fewer bugs more frequently.
- Optimized the core game loop with about 80% letting us run a lot more instances of the game on the same server.
- Implemented a code review process using pull requests, this increased the programming teams
 knowledge of other parts of the code base and letting us catch bugs before they caused any
 problems for the rest of the team.

Bertil Bergbom & Söner AB, Factory worker

Dec 2010 - Aug 2012

Some basic programming to make sure products came out with the correct measurements.

EDUCATION

University of Skövde, Skövde Sweden

2012 - 2016

B.S. in information technology with a focus on computer game development

AWARDS

Sweden Game Awards: Best Scenario

GRiEF (student project)

Skövde Academic Game Award

GRiEF (student project)

2013